Joshua Logan Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1907-1989 (Box 16-40)
  - “N” miscellaneous, 1931, 1940-1941, 1948-1988, undated, (4 folders)
  - Olaf, Pierre, 1966, 1985, undated
  - Olivier, Laurence, 1955-1959, 1974
  - Osborn, Paul, 1940, 1953-1963, 1975-1976, undated (Box 32)
  - “O” miscellaneous, 1940, 1949-1979, 1986-1987, undated, (2 folders)
  - Patrick, John, 1948, 1976-1977, 1984, undated
  - Pearl S. Buck Foundation, 1965-1969, undated
  - Peck, Gregory, 1958, 1975-1976
  - Pinza, Ezio, 1950-1957, 1976, undated
  - Players Club, New York, N.Y., 1948-1974, 1985-1987
  - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J.
    - 1930-1965, (2 folders)
    - 1966-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - “P” miscellaneous, 1940, 1948-1987, undated, (5 folders)
  - Quinn, Anthony, 1958-1961, undated
  - “Q” miscellaneous, 1953-1960, 1966, 1975, undated
  - Redgrave, Vanessa, 1968-1975, undated
  - Reed, Rex, 1971-1976
  - Reed, William Garrard, 1930-1931, 1940-1948, 1960-1964, 1976-1980, undated
  - Reynolds, Burt, 1974, 1987, undated (Box 34)
  - Rittman, Trude, 1949-1955, 1976, undated
  - River Club, New York, N.Y., 1960-1963, 1972-1978, 1985, undated
  - Robinson, Edward G., 1956
  - Rockefeller family, 1950-1978, undated
  - Rodgers, Richard and Dorothy, 1939, 1945-1982, undated
  - Romanoff, Michael, 1961-1963, 1986, undated
  - Rome, Harold and Florence, 1955-1972, undated
  - Roosevelt family, 1953-1961
  - Rosengarten, Leonard M. and Frances, 1963-1970, undated
  - Rule, Janice, 1953-1954, 1974, 1986, undated
  - Russell, Rosalind, 1952-1976, undated
  - “Ra-Ri” miscellaneous, 1940, 1948-1988, undated, (2 folders)
  - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous, 1929, 1940, 1948-1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Schlee, George and Valentina, 1953-1964, 1985, undated
  - Scofield, Maurice, 1958-1961, 1972-1985, undated
  - Seidman, Ginette See Container 35, Spanier, Ginette
  - Selznick family, 1949, 1955-1969, undated
  - Shaw, George, 1954, 1968-1976, 1986, undated
  - Sinatra, Frank, 1953, 1965-1968, 1980-1987, undated
  - Spanier, Ginette, 1950-1976, 1982-1985, undated
  - Stamford, Conn., 1953-1969, 1984, undated
  - Stanley, Kim, 1953-1955
  - Starr, Milton, 1950-1959, 1966, undated
  - Stewart, James, 1947-1948, 1960, 1970-1987, undated
  - Stickney, Dorothy, 1949-1950, 1964-1969, 1984, undated
  - Strasberg, Lee and Paula, 1949, 1956-1969, undated
  - Sullivan, Ed, 1953-1960, undated
  - Swope family, 1949-1955, 1962-1964, 1970-1975, undated
  - “Sa-St” miscellaneous, 1935-1987, undated, (5 folders) (Box 36)
  - “Su-Sz” miscellaneous, 1948-1975, 1986-1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Taradash, Daniel, 1955-1960, 1968-1972, 1987, undated
  - Theatre Guild, 1948-1963, 1977, undated
  - “T” miscellaneous, 1940, 1947-1987, undated, (4 folders)
  - United Service Organizations, 1953-1966, 1982-1985
  - “U” miscellaneous, 1948-1970, 1976, 1982-1985, undated
  - Vance, Vivian, 1965-1967, undated
  - “V” miscellaneous, 1950-1969, 1975-1987, undated (Box 38)
  - Warner, Jack, 1954-1968, 1986, undated
  - Wasserman, Lew, 1948-1957, 1986-1987, undated
  - Whitehead, Robert, 1949-1950, 1956-1958, 1965, 1973, 1980-1982, undated
  - Williams, Emlyn and Molly, 1945-1977, 1983-1988, undated, (2 folders)
  - Williams, Tennessee, 1949, 1955, undated
  - Winchell, Walter, 1953-1962, undated
  - “W-Wa” miscellaneous, 1940-1988, undated
  - “We-Wz” miscellaneous, 1940-1988, undated, (4 folders) (Box 39)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1954-1956, 1963-1969, undated
  - “Y” miscellaneous, 1949-1963, 1978, 1985-1987, undated
  - “Z” miscellaneous, 1950-1961, 1968-1978, 1984, undated, (2 folders)
  - Unidentified
    - 1907, 1925-1931, 1938-1952
    - 1953-1987, undated, (5 folders) (Box 40)
- Business Papers, 1930-1989 (Box 41-96)
  Correspondence, financial data, interoffice memoranda, legal papers, office diaries, and notes.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Agents (Box 41)
    - Actors' agents, 1941-1985, undated
    - Booking agents
      - Arthur Cantor, 1980, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1977-1981
      - Royce Carlton, 1983-1986, undated, (7 folders)
      - W. Colston Leigh
        - 1965-1967
        - 1974-1979, (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Literary agents, 1940-1986, undated, (7 folders)
    - Personal agents (Box 43)
      - Chasin-Citron-Park Agency, 1964-1965
      - Frank Goodman, 1957
      - Irving Paul Lazar, 1958-1983, (2 folders)
      - Pickman Co., 1968-1969
      - William Morris Agency, 1955-1972
    - Publicity agents, 1980
  - Art and antiques
    - 1945-1984, (5 folders)
    - Undated (Box 44)
  - Employment
    - Applications for production work, 1947-1987, undated, (4 folders)
    - Applications from actors
      - Oct. 1940-July 1952, (5 folders)
      - Aug. 1952-May 1988, (7 folders) (Box 45)
  - Office and household staff, 1950-1975, 1987, (3 folders)
  - Financial papers (Box 46)
    - Annual statements
      - 1938-1951, (9 folders)
      - 1952-1957, (6 folders) (Box 47)
      - 1958-1962, (6 folders) (Box 48)
      - 1963-1976, (11 folders) (Box 49)
    - Banks
      - Bank of America, Beverly Hills, Calif., 1955-1969, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1975, 1987
      - Security Bank and Trust Co., Stamford, Conn., 1955-1956
      - Stamford Trust Co., Stamford, Conn., 1953-1961 (Box 50)
      - Union Savings Bank, Danbury, Conn., 1950-1956
      - United States National Bank of Oregon, 1968-1969, undated
    - Bernard Reis and Co.
      - 1950-1960, (10 folders)
      - 1961-1965, (5 folders) (Box 51)
    - Investments
      - Fuel industries
        - 1949-1977, (3 folders)
        - 1978-1987, (3 folders) (Box 52)
      - Irving Trust Co.
        - General
          - 1948-1972, (6 folders)
          - 1973-1985, undated (Box 53)
        - Loan, 1964-1977, (2 folders)
      - Kidder, Peabody and Co., 1931-1976, 1987, (2 folders)
      - Lehman Brothers
        - 1955-1969, (4 folders)
        - 1970-1979 (Box 54)
      - Lomer Corp., 1954-1956
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1980
      - Pleasance Flowers, 1952-1959, 1965, (2 folders)
      - Shows
        - 110 in the Shade, 1973-1976
        - All in One, 1955
        - Anne of the Thousand Days, 1949
        - Arms and the Girl, 1949-1950
        - The Bat, 1952-1953
        - Bells Are Ringing, 1956-1960
        - Billy Budd, 1951
        - Burning Bright, 1950-1951
        - By the Beautiful Sea, 1954
        - Call Me Madam, 1950-1952
        - The Changing Room, 1973-1974
        - The Detective Story, 1949-1976
        - Don't Call Back, 1974-1975 (Box 55)
        - Equus, 1974-1976, (2 folders)
        - Gypsy, 1959, 1972-1979
        - Hello Dolly, 1963-1973
        - Irma La Douce, 1960-1975
        - Keep Off the Grass, 1972
        - The King and I, 1951-1955, (2 folders)
        - The Magnificent Seven, 1955-1970, (3 folders)
        - Manhattan Follies, 1974 (Box 56)
        - Miscellaneous, 1940, 1949-1986, (3 folders)
        - A Musical Jubilee, 1975-1976
        - Oliver, 1973-1975
        - On the Wing, 1954-1955
        - Peter Pan, 1949-1985
        - Portrait of a Lady, 1954
        - Remains to Be Seen, 1951
        - Seventh Heaven, 1955
        - Stephen D, 1967
        - Take Me Along, 1975-1976
        - Tall Story, 1958-1959
        - A Tree Grows in Brooklyn, 1951
        - Trick, 1978
        - Twigs, 1971-1976
        - Wonderful Town, 1953
      - Theater companies (Box 57)
        - General, 1953-1955
        - Joshua Logan Dinner Theatre, 1982
    - Lazarow and Co., 1965-1976, (6 folders)
    - Taxes, 1948-1988, (4 folders) (Box 58)
  - Insurance
    - 1942-1960, (4 folders)
    - 1961-1981, 1987, undated, (6 folders) (Box 59)
  - Interoffice memoranda
    - 1940, Sept. 1948-Aug. 1953, (3 folders)
    - Sept. 1953-Feb. 1957, (10 folders) (Box 60)
    - Mar. 1957-June 1965, (10 folders) (Box 61)
    - Jan. 1966-Sept. 1973, (10 folders) (Box 62)
    - June 1974-July 1985, undated, (4 folders) (Box 63)
  - Legal papers
    - Adoptions, 1949-1952
    - Becker, Berman and Odell, 1949-1952
    - Fitelson and Mayers
      - 1952-1967, (7 folders)
      - 1968-1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 64)
    - Lawsuits (Bette Davis, Rex Reed), 1976-1978
    - Miscellany, 1936-1982
    - Wills, 1940, 1951-1952, 1960, 1966-1988, (4 folders)
  - Office diaries
    - Sept. 1949-May 1950, (2 folders)
    - June 1950-May 1952, (5 folders) (Box 65)
    - June 1952-May 1954, (6 folders) (Box 66)
    - June 1954-Sept. 1956, (7 folders) (Box 67)
    - Oct. 1956-Dec. 1959, (8 folders) (Box 68)
    - Jan. 1960-Aug. 1962, (7 folders) (Box 69)
    - Sept. 1962-Aug. 1964, (6 folders) (Box 70)
    - Sept. 1964-Aug. 1966, (7 folders) (Box 71)
    - Sept. 1966-June 1969, (7 folders) (Box 72)
    - July 1969-Dec. 1971, (6 folders) (Box 73)
    - Jan. 1972-Dec. 1973, (6 folders) (Box 74)
    - Jan. 1974-June 1976, (6 folders) (Box 75)
    - July 1976-Dec. 1977, (6 folders) (Box 76)
    - Jan. 1978-Oct. 1979, (7 folders) (Box 77)
    - Nov. 1979-May 1980, (8 folders) (Box 78)
    - June 1980-May 1982, (8 folders) (Box 79)
    - Jan. 1982-Sept. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 80)
    - Oct. 1983-Dec. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 81)
    - Jan.-Dec. 1985, (6 folders) (Box 82)
    - Jan.-May 1986, (1 folder) (Box 83)
    - June 1986-Oct. 1988, (6 folders)
  - Organizations (Box 84)
    - Actors Equity Association, 1943-1983, undated
    - Actors' Fund of America, 1948-1988, undated, (3 folders)
    - American Society of Composers, 1976-1985
    - An American Theatre Ensemble, 1975
    - Authors' League of America, 1940-1975
    - Chorus Equity Association of America, 1952-1953
    - Directors Guild of America, 1960-1968, 1975-1987, (2 folders)
    - Joshua Logan Enterprises, 1950-1953
    - Logan Foundation
      - May 1950-Feb. 1951
      - Mar. 1951-May 1959, (8 folders) (Box 85)
      - June 1959-Apr. 1975, (9 folders) (Box 86)
      - Apr. 1975-Jan. 1988, undated, (2 folders) (Box 87)
    - Logan Memorial Fund, 1988
    - Mansfield Music Co., 1984-1985
    - Mansfield Productions
      - Contracts, 1956-1964, (2 folders)
      - Fonda, Jane, 1959-1962
      - General, 1956-1969, (2 folders)
      - Simmons, Floyd, 1957-1958, undated, (2 folders)
    - Screen Directors' Guild of America, 1955
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1955-1984, undated
    - Writers Guild of America, West, 1965-1970
  - Projects, pending
    - Miscellaneous
      - Cuban story, 1952-1953
      - Egyptian film, 1964
      - Hammerstein, Oscar, tribute
        - Jan.-Feb. 1971
        - Mar. 1971-Nov. 1972, (2 folders) (Box 88)
      - Kabuki theater, 1949-1969, undated, (7 folders)
      - Kahn, Bernie, You'll Never Guess Who Died Today, 1972
      - Motion picture ideas, 1956-1959, undated
      - Play ideas, 1952-1957, 1986, undated
      - Proposals under consideration
        - 1940-1953, (2 folders)
        - 1954-1987, undated, (4 folders) (Box 89)
      - Reading lists
        - General, 1952-1962, (5 folders)
        - Gillmore, Margalo, 1960-1962, undated
  - Projects, pending
    - Miscellaneous
      - Scripts submitted, correspondence about
        - 1939-1952
        - 1953-1967, (11 folders) (Box 90)
        - 1968-1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 91)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Co., charm school, 1966-1971, undated, (2 folders)
      - Ten best plays list, 1976
    - Properties
      - The Admiral Perry Story, 1955
      - At Your Service, 1965
      - The Baker's Wife, 1961-1964
      - Birdman of Alcatraz, 1956-1960, (2 folders)
      - The Careful Man, 1961-1962
      - The Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1958-1959, undated
      - Far Away the Train-Birds Cry, 1959-1960
      - The Fortune Finders, 1956-1966
      - Helen of Troy, 1952-1954
      - The Innocent Bystander, 1946
      - Little Joe
        - 1965-1966
        - Undated (Box 92)
      - Look Homeward Angel, 1930-1969, undated
      - Love Me Monday, 1959
      - The Magic Bed-Knob, 1949-1964, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960, undated
      - Mistress Masham's Repose, 1946-1972, (3 folders)
      - A Month in the Country, 1949
      - Motive, 1971-1972
      - Out by the Country Club, 1950-1963
      - Rear Window, 1950-1954
      - The Sobbin' Women, 1948-1952, undated (Box 93)
      - That River of Gold, 1959-1976, undated
      - This Gentle Ghost, 1940
    - Public appearances
      - Lectures, 1953-1985, (2 folders)
      - Radio and television, 1949-1983, undated, (2 folders)
      - Teaching
        - Florida Atlantic University, Boca Raton, Fla., 1983-1989, (2 folders)
        - Joshua Logan Workshop, New York, N. Y., 1955
        - Miscellany, 1976-1981
  - Real estate
    - Brookfield, Conn., 1944-1985
    - California, 1955-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Chelsea Embankment, London, Eng., 1972-1978, (2 folders)
    - Hawaii, 1956-1968
    - Jamaica, British West Indies, 1952-1959, (2 folders)
    - Long Ridge, Stamford, Conn.
      - 1942-1967, (3 folders)
      - 1968-1987, undated (Box 95)
    - Miscellany, 1947-1987, undated
    - Redcliffe Gardens, London, Eng., 1977-1981, (2 folders)
    - River House, New York, N. Y., 1950-1987, (3 folders)
    - Wildwood, Stamford, Conn., 1954-1960
  - Travel
    - China, 1972
    - Cuba, 1940
    - France and Switzerland, 1953-1960, undated
    - Miscellany, 1949-1984, undated
    - Shipping and customs, 1952-1966, undated, (3 folders) (Box 96)
    - Travel documents, 1939-1963, 1979
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1958-1963, undated, (3 folders)
    - World trip, 1951-1952, undated
- Production File, 1903-1989 (Box 96-129)
  Blueprints, correspondence, financial data, legal papers, memoranda, newspaper clippings, notes, and printed material relating to productions with which Logan was associated.
  Arranged alphabetically by title of production and therein by type of material.
  - Act One (Box 96)
    - Casting, 1960-1961, undated
    - Financial papers, 1960-1961
    - General correspondence, 1958-1961, undated
    - Legal papers, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
    - Publicity, 1959-1961
    - Research material, circa 1960
    - Working papers, script, 1959-1961
  - All American
    - Casting, 1961-1962
    - Financial papers
      - Investors, 1961-1962
      - Royalties, 1975-1980 (Box 97)
    - General correspondence, 1961-1962, undated
    - Legal papers, 1961-1962
    - Publicity, 1961-1962
    - Reviews, 1962
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1961-1962
      - Script, 1961-1962, undated
      - Technical, 1961-1962, undated
  - Annie Get Your Gun
    - Financial papers, 1948
    - General correspondence, 1947
    - Legal papers, 1945-1947
    - Other productions, 1948-1949
    - Publicity, 1947, undated
    - Reviews, 1946
    - Working papers, technical, undated
  - As the Lady Said to the Sailor
    - Casting, 1972
    - General correspondence, 1971-1972
    - Legal papers, 1972
    - Working papers, script, undated
  - Baker Street
    - Casting, 1963
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1963
      - Investors, 1963-1965
      - Statements, 1965
    - General correspondence, 1963-1965
    - Legal papers, 1963
    - Publicity, 1963
    - Working papers, script, 1963
  - The Better Angels (Box 98)
    - Casting, 1952
    - Publicity, 1952
    - Working papers, script, 1952
  - Blue Denim
    - Casting, 1958
    - Financial papers
      - Investors, 1956-1960
      - Royalties, 1958
      - Statements, 1958-1959, undated
    - General correspondence, 1957-1958
    - Legal papers, 1956-1957
    - Publicity, 1957-1958
    - Reviews, 1958-1959
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1958, undated
      - Technical, 1957, undated
  - Blue Star
    - Casting, 1961
    - General correspondence, 1961-1962
    - Legal papers, 1961-1963, (3 folders)
    - Publicity, 1961, undated
    - Research material, 1961, undated
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1961, undated
      - Technical, 1961
  - Breakfast at Tiffany's, legal papers, 1965
  - Bus Stop (Box 99)
    - Casting, 1955-1956, undated
    - Financial papers, 1955-1973
    - General correspondence, 1956-1975, undated
    - Legal papers, 1956
    - Publicity, 1956-1987 See also Oversize
    - Reviews, 1956
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1956, undated
      - Technical, 1956
  - By Jupiter, financial papers, statements, 1942
  - Camelot
    - Casting, 1966, undated
    - Financial papers, 1966-1967
    - General correspondence, 1966-1968
    - Legal papers, 1966
    - Other productions, 1967-1984
    - Publicity, 1966-1967, 1981, undated, (3 folders)
    - Reviews, 1967-1981
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1962-1967
      - Technical, 1966-1967, (2 folders)
  - Camille, publicity, 1933
  - Careful! (He Might Hear You) (Box 100)
    - Casting, 1964-1974, (3 folders)
    - Financial papers, 1963-1974 See also Oversize
    - General correspondence, 1963-1983, (5 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1963-1982, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1970-1971, undated (Box 101)
    - Publicity, 1963-1984, undated
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1963-1969, undated
      - Technical, 1968-1972, undated
  - Carmen
    - General correspondence, 1951-1983, undated
    - Publicity, circa 1982
    - Working papers, script, 1958-1982, undated
  - Carry Nation, reviews, 1932
  - Charley's Aunt
    - Financial papers, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1940-1941
    - Legal papers, 1940
    - Miscellany, undated
    - Other productions, 1963-1982
    - Publicity, 1940-1948, undated
    - Reviews, 1940
    - Working papers, performance, circa 1940
  - Cherry
    - Casting, 1972-1978, undated, (2 folders)
    - Financial papers, 1972-1973, undated
    - General correspondence, 1972-1978, undated, (2 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1972-1978 (Box 102)
    - Publicity, 1978
    - Reviews, 1978
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1973-1978, undated, (2 folders)
      - Technical, 1973
  - Child's Play
    - Casting, 1971
    - General correspondence, 1971
    - Working papers, circa 1971
  - Clarence, publicity, undated
  - The Corn is Green See Containers 114-116, Miss Moffat
  - The Day I Forgot
    - Publicity, 1933
    - Reviews, 1933
  - The Emperor Jones, reviews, undated
  - Ensign Pulver
    - Casting, 1963
    - Financial papers
      - General, 1963-1966
      - Royalties, 1964-1985, (6 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1963-1964
    - Legal papers, 1963-1964 (Box 103)
    - Publicity, 1963-1981
    - Research material, undated
    - Reviews, 1964
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1963
      - Technical, 1963
  - Epitaph for George Dillon
    - Casting, 1958
    - Financial papers, 1958
    - General correspondence, 1958
    - Legal papers, 1958
    - Publicity, 1958, undated
    - Reviews, 1958
  - Escadrille
    - Casting, 1966-1969, undated
    - General correspondence, 1969
    - Legal papers, 1968-1972
    - Working papers
      - Script, undated
      - Technical, 1969
  - Fanny (play)
    - Casting, 1954-1956, undated, (4 folders)
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1953-1955, (2 folders)
      - Investors, 1953-1959, (2 folders) (Box 104)
      - Royalties, 1954-1966
      - Statements, 1954-1975, (3 folders)
      - Taxes, 1954-1959
    - General correspondence, 1954-1956, (3 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1953-1966, (2 folders)
    - Other productions (Box 105)
      - General, 1955-1986, (2 folders)
      - Germany, 1955-1957
      - Great Britain, 1955-1957
    - Publicity, 1954-1966, (2 folders)
    - Reviews, 1954
    - Tickets, 1954-1955, (3 folders)
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1954
      - Script
        - 1953-1955, (3 folders)
        - Undated (Box 106)
      - Technical, 1953-1955
  - Fanny (film)
    - Casting, 1957-1960, undated
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1960-1961
      - General, 1958-1975, undated
      - Royalties, 1958-1978, undated
      - Statements
        - Mar. 1960-Nov. 1963, (6 folders)
        - Jan. 1964-Nov. 1972, (5 folders) (Box 107)
    - General correspondence, 1955-1973, (2 folders)
    - Legal papers
      - Mar. 1956-Oct. 1959, (5 folders)
      - Mar. 1960-May 1981, (4 folders) (Box 108)
    - Publicity, 1959-1961, undated, (2 folders)
    - Reviews, 1961
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1959-1961, undated
      - Technical, 1960-1961
  - A Gala Tribute to Joshua Logan
    - General correspondence, 1974-1975
    - Legal papers, 1975
    - Publicity, 1975
    - Reviews, 1975
    - Working papers, script, 1975
  - Garden of Allah
    - General correspondence, 1936
    - Legal papers, 1936
  - Georgia Boy, legal papers, 1945
  - Happy Birthday
    - Legal papers, 1946-1948
    - Other productions, 1948-1951
    - Publicity, 1946-1950
    - Reviews, 1946, undated
  - Harrigan and Hart
    - Casting, 1964, undated
    - Financial papers, 1964-1985, undated
    - General correspondence
      - 1903, 1954-1965
      - 1966-1986, undated (Box 109)
    - Legal papers, 1955-1985, undated
    - Publicity, 1953-1985
    - Research material, 1927-1977, undated, (4 folders)
    - Reviews, 1984-1985
    - Tickets, 1984-1985
    - Working papers, script, 1955-1984, undated
  - Higher and Higher
    - Legal papers, 1940
    - Publicity, 1940
  - Horowitz and Mrs. Washington
    - Casting, 1980
    - General correspondence, 1979-1980
    - Legal papers, 1979
    - Publicity, 1980
    - Reviews, 1980
    - Working papers, script, 1979-1980
  - Hot September (Box 110)
    - Casting, 1964-1981
    - Financial papers, 1965
    - General correspondence, 1965-1985
    - Legal papers, 1965-1981
    - Publicity, 1965, undated
    - Reviews, 1965
    - Working papers
      - Performance, undated
      - Script, 1981, undated
  - Huck and Jim
    - Casting, 1983-1986, undated, (3 folders)
    - Financial papers, 1983, undated
    - General correspondence, 1950-1987, (2 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1983-1985
    - Publicity, 1983-1986
    - Reviews, 1983
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1950-1951, 1983-1987, (3 folders)
      - Technical, 1951-1986, undated (Box 111)
  - I Married an Angel
    - Legal papers, 1938-1939
    - Publicity, 1938
    - Reviews, 1938
  - I Met My Love Again
    - Publicity, 1938
    - Reviews, 1938
  - John Loves Mary
    - Legal papers, 1946
    - Publicity, 1947
    - Reviews, 1947
    - Working papers, script, 1947
  - Jonathan Wild
    - Casting, 1971-1972, undated
    - Financial papers, 1971-1972
    - General correspondence, 1971-1985, (3 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1971-1973
    - Publicity, 1972
    - Working papers, script, 1971-1972, undated
  - Journey, legal papers, 1977
  - Kind Sir
    - Casting, 1952-1953, undated
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1953-1954, undated, (2 folders)
      - General, 1953-1955
      - Investors, 1952-1955
      - Royalties, 1953-1955
      - Statements, 1953-1954
    - General correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 112)
    - Legal papers, 1952-1954
    - Publicity, 1953-1954
    - Reviews, 1953-1954
    - Tickets, 1953-1954
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1953
      - Script, 1952-1953, undated
      - Technical, 1953-1954, undated See also Oversize
  - Knickerbocker Holiday
    - Casting, 1970
    - Legal papers, 1938
    - Publicity, 1938-1939
    - Reviews, 1938-1939
  - Look to the Lillies
    - Financial papers, 1970
    - General correspondence, 1970
    - Legal papers, 1969-1970
    - Publicity, 1970
    - Reviews, 1970
    - Tickets, 1970
  - Lord Pengo, publicity, 1962
  - Let Us Be Gay, reviews, 1932
  - Lysistrata, publicity, 1931, 1979
  - Mame
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1965-1966
      - Royalties
        - May 1966-Oct. 1969, (2 folders)
        - Nov. 1969-July 1985, (5 folders) (Box 113)
      - Taxes, 1970
    - Legal papers, 1965-1976, (4 folders)
    - Other productions, 1968-1969
    - Publicity, 1957
  - The Merry Partners See Containers 108-109, Harrigan and Hart
  - Middle of the Night
    - Casting, 1955-1957